Spotlight™ on IBM® DB2® LUW is a component of the Toad DBA Suite for IBM DB2 LUW that diagnoses performance problems in real time through a unique and intuitive user interface. Through a visual representation of the process flows within your IBM DB2 database, you can easily pinpoint the source of a performance problem and resolve it quickly with Toad for IBM DB2 LUW or SQL Optimizer for IBM DB2 LUW.