The Toad® DBA Suite for SQL Server installer is applicable for the following editions: 
•	Toad DBA Suite for SQL Server 

Your Toad DBA Suite for SQL Server license key determines the edition and will enable the appropriate functionality accordingly.

The Toad® DBA Suite for SQL Server consists of:
•	Toad for SQL Server Xpert (includes Quest® SQL Optimizer for SQL Server) 
•	Toad® Data Modeler
•	Spotlight® on SQL Server Desktop Edition
•	Benchmark Factory® for Databases – SQL Server Edition

Whether you are a new or experienced Toad user, visit Toad World at www.toadworld.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
