The Toad® Development Suite for SQL Server consists of:
•	Toad for SQL Server Xpert (includes Quest® SQL Optimizer for SQL Server)
•	Benchmark Factory® for Databases – SQL Server Edition.  

Whether you are a new or experienced Toad user, visit Toad World at www.toadworld.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
