The Toad™ for IBM® DB2® LUW Suite installer consists of:

•	Toad for IBM DB2 LUW Xpert (includes SQL Optimizer for IBM® DB2® LUW)
•	Benchmark Factory™ for Databases – IBM DB2 Edition

Your Toad for IBM DB2 LUW license key determines the edition and will enable Toad for IBM DB2 LUW functionality accordingly.

Whether you are a new or experienced Toad user, visit Toad World at www.toadworld.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
