The Toad™  BI Suite Server installer installs Toad™  Intelligence Central, Toad™  Intelligence Central Admin.  In addition, the server installer installs a copy of Toad™  Data Point Pro on the server to enhance the ODBC library available to Toad™  Intelligence Central.

Your Toad™  BI Suite license key enables the correct functionality and number of users allowed to utilize the Toad™  BI Suite products. 

Whether you are a new or experienced Toad™  user, visit Toad™  World at www.Toad™ world.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
