The Toad™  BI Suite Server installer installs the desktop products in Toad™  BI Suite:  Toad™  Data Point Professional, Toad™  Decision Point Professional and Toad™  Intelligence Central Admin.  

The Toad™  BI Suite Trial products come with a 90-day trial license for an unlimited number of users.

Whether you are a new or experienced Toad™  user, visit Toad™  World at www.Toad™ world.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
