The Toad® Development Suite for Oracle consists of:
•	Toad for Oracle Xpert (includes Quest® SQL Optimizer for Oracle)
•	Quest® Code Tester for Oracle
•	Benchmark Factory® for Databases – Oracle Edition.  

With Toad for Oracle (all editions) you get FREE access to:
•	Toad® for Data Analysts Base:  querying, reporting and data management tool for multiple dbs (Oracle, SQL Server, DB2, MySQL, Sybase, Teradata, Netezza, PostgreSQL, Access, Vertica and ODBC)
•	Toad® Data Modeler: Physical and logical data modeling tool for Oracle, SQL Server, DB2, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Access and Ingres.


Whether you are a new or experienced Toad user, visit Toad World at www.toadworld.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
