The Toad™ for IBM® DB2® LUW installer is applicable for the following editions: 
 
•	Toad for IBM DB2  LUW Base
•	Toad for IBM DB2  LUW Professional
•	DB Admin Module

Your Toad for IBM DB2  LUW license key determines the edition and will enable Toad for IBM DB2  LUW functionality accordingly.

Whether you are a new or experienced Toad user, visit Toad World at www.toadworld.com, your one-stop resource for education, expertise and collaboration.

Please click Next to continue with the installation.
