Spotlight® on Oracle is a component of the Toad DBA Suite for Oracle that diagnoses performance problems in real time through a unique and intuitive user interface. Through a visual representation of the process flows within your Oracle database, you can easily pinpoint the source of a performance problem and resolve it quickly with Toad for Oracle or Quest SQL Optimizer for Oracle.
Spotlight on Oracle integrates Spotlight on UNIX/Linux/Windows and Spotlight on MySQL.
