Benchmark Factory™ is a database replay and performance testing tool that stress tests your environment by simulating users and SQL transactions on the database. Developers and QA professionals use Benchmark Factory and Toad® to test SQL and database code against development SLAs and scalability. DBAs use Benchmark Factory™ and Toad® to replay database workload or utilize industry standard benchmarks to mitigate the risks of database upgrades, migrations or patch releases.