Toad® for Data Analysts Base Edition is a multi-platform query and reporting tool built for anyone that needs to query databases and report on the results. You can easily access data from practically any database platform and quickly produce reports. With Toad for Data Analysts Base Edition, you can even join tables across platforms! 

Toad® for Data Analysts Base Edition is now available for use with all editions of Toad for Oracle.

This promotion may be subject to change at Quest’s discretion. Please note that installation and optimization may take 10 minutes or more.
