Quest™ SQL Optimizer for Oracle is a powerful extension to Toad for Oracle offering a fully-automated approach to maximizing SQL performance. It validates database code to ensure the best possible performance through proactive identification of potential issues and automation of SQL tuning based on re-writing technology. SQL Optimizer analyzes database workload and offers index recommendations as well as providing the ability to analyze the performance impact of database changes.