SQL Navigator™ provides an integrated environment for developing and testing Oracle stored programs and procedures, schemas, objects, SQL scripts, and more-all from an easy-to-easy graphical user interface. The SQL Navaigator family of products is a complete development environment for Oracle server-side development and management. It has been conceived, designed and developed by Oracle developers and DBAs with hands-on experience in the most common problems facing Oracle developers. 