Benchmark Factory™ is a database replay and performance testing tool that stress tests your environment by simulating users and SQL transactions on the database. Developers and QA professionals use Benchmark Factory and Toad to test SQL and database code against development SLAs and scalability. DBAs use Benchmark Factory™ and Toad™ to replay database workload or utilize industry standard benchmarks to mitigate the risks of database upgrades, migrations or patch releases.