Welcome to Toad TM   Meet Toad Intelligence Central — a complementary server technology to Toad for Oracle that lets your development teams dramatically improve their ability to collaborate coding standards to drive down cost and risk.   Toad Intelligence Central enables you to integrate Oracle database development with your Continuous Integration (CI) processes. By centralizing your PL/SQL unit test execution and code review automations, created in Toad, they become callable from CI servers such as Jenkins.   For more information, please read this Toad World blog.