Spotlight® on Oracle diagnoses performance problems in real time through a unique and intuitive user interface. Through a visual representation of the process flows within your Oracle database, you can easily pinpoint the source of a performance problem and resolve it quickly with Toad® for Oracle or Quest™ SQL Optimizer for Oracle. Includes Predictive Diagnostics.
Spotlight on Oracle includes Spotlight on UNIX/Linux/Windows and Spotlight on MySQL.
