Quest™ SQL Optimizer for Oracle is a powerful extension to Toad for Oracle offering a fully-automated approach to maximizing SQL performance. It validates database code to ensure the best possible performance through proactive identification of potential issues and automation of SQL tuning. SQL Optimizer analyzes database workload and offers index recommendations and provides the ability to analyze the performance impact of database changes.