Toad® for Data Analysts a cross-platform query and data integration tool that simplifies data access, analysis and provisioning for data management professionals.  It is specifically built for data analysts, providing nearly limitless data connectivity, desktop data integration, visual query building, and workflow automation.
Toad® for Data Analysts Base Edition is now available for use with all editions of Toad for Oracle.

This promotion may be subject to change at Quest’s discretion. 
