With Toad™ for MySQL, developers and database administrators can use a familiar, proven tool to manage their MySQL databases. Toad for MySQL empowers developers and administrators of varying skill levels, to rapidly create and execute queries, automate database object management and develop SQL code on MySQL databases more efficiently. Toad for MySQL is a free tool. Support and documentation for this product is available through the community at www.toadworld.com